Guy Berkovich

Full Stack Developer

About Me

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with a wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Work well independently and in teams, deep technological understanding and self-taught with excellent technical abilities offering 4 years of related experience.

Contact

Address: Tel Aviv, IL Phone: +972 54 811 4540 Email: Mailofguy@gmail.com

Links:

<u>LinkedIn</u><u>Portfolio Site</u>

GitHub

Technology Stack

Front End:

- JavaScript + TypeScript
- React
- JQuery
- Css, scss, sass

Back End:

- Node.js
- Php
- Java
- python

DataBase:

- MySql
- Mongodb
- Redis
- Postgresql

Experience

NetoMedia - Full Stack Developer

2020 - PRESENT

- Developed multi-brand website using React and Node.js.
- Improved site speed by extensive code refactoring, webpack configuration optimization and lazy loading.
- Built extensive test coverage for old and new features which reduced the number of bugs and customer complaints.

ProGeeks - Full Stack Developer

2017 - 2020

- Worked on several projects in the web environment including 2 startups from scratch.
- Delivered performance-driven and user-centric websites that met all business requirements.
- Developed systems independently or with teams in modern technologies like Node.js React php JS vanilla and sapui5.
- Leading a multi layered development process from scratch to final delivery.
- Took initial concepts and developed project plans.

Languages

Hebrew - native language **English** - very good

Education

John Bryce college - Mobile application development

2016 - 2017

- Mobile and responsive web applications development for Android and iOS.
- Creating and interfacing with external APIs and local or external databases with SQLite and mySql.